[{"question": "  ross, when\u0092s this comet thing start?", "answer": " well, technically it seven billion years ago\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " okay! okay! fine, i\u0092ll stop! no teaching, okay? we\u0092ll just watch the pretty light streaking across the sky.  okay? who\u0092s official name is bapstein-king.", "answer": " okay! okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  there it is! oh, look at that! isn\u0092t mother nature amazing?", "answer": "  that\u0092s a plane!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " well, all right. 1700 bags of peanuts flying that high, that\u0092s pretty amazing too.", "answer": " hey, i wonder if you can see my apartment from up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " no. no, you can\u0092t.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh i don\u0092t-i don\u0092t know.", "answer": " man, look at all those stars!  infinite space. it really, really makes you wonder, doesn\u0092t", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  y\u0092know what else makes you wonder?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  no, i\u0092m not!", "answer": " then why are you wearing monica\u0092s jacket?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah actually, i think we\u0092re gonna take off too. we rented a movie.", "answer": " oh! i won\u0092t say, \u0091no\u0092 to a movie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " uh pheebs, we just actually kinda wanted to be alone.", "answer": " shh! get me out of here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  ross!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " come here, check this out!", "answer": " what? is it the comet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " joey come\u0097i can\u0092t believe\u0097i bring you here to see the bapstein-king comet, one of nature\u0092s most spectacular phenomenon, and all you care about are bugs stuck in tar and-and some woman!", "answer": "  y\u0092know, there\u0092s two women dude.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " show me where?", "answer": " right-right up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  joey where\u0092s the pipe that was holding the door open?", "answer": "  i don\u0092t know!   yeah, i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " joey!", "answer": " what?! all right\u0097hey! don\u0092t look at me! you\u0092re the one who wanted to come up and look for some stupid burger king comet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " it\u0092s called the bapstein-king comet, okay?  hey! hey! bapstein was a very well respected astronomer!", "answer": "  oh no! no! no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  monica!", "answer": " she\u0092s sleeping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i know, just quick-quick question, quick question. which one was deep impact and which one was armageddon?", "answer": " deep impact was the one with robert duval, armageddon is what\u0092s going to happen to you if you wake me up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " it is in the living room where there is also a light! and no one will kick you in the shin.", "answer": " what?!  ow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  please don\u0092t be a space ship. please don\u0092t be a space ship.  oh thank god!  how could you be beeping?! i just disconnected you! i took out your battery! how can\u009a", "answer": " beep!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " rachel!! monica!!", "answer": " come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe this!!", "answer": " all right well, y\u0092know\u009ai guess we know what we have to do to get down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  yeah, i guess we don\u0092t have a choice.  help us! please help us! we\u0092re stuck up on the roof and we can\u0092t get down!!!", "answer": " ross. i was thinking we could just go down the fire escape.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " shhhhhhhhh!!!  i\u0092m sorry, i thought maybe i\u0092d make some warm milk and it would help me sleep.", "answer": " with a wok?  i thought you were going to read my boring book to put you asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " it got interesting! damn you oprah!", "answer": " here, let me make the milk, i\u0092m up anyway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hey, y\u0092know what we can do? y\u0092know, now that we are up? we can just like talk to each other all night long, y\u0092know like we did when we were first going out. it\u0092d be fun!", "answer": " okay that does sound like fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay, so how bummed were you when the second sister died huh?", "answer": " the second sister dies?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  no. no, i-i was, i was talking about the book i was reading.", "answer": " the second sister dies in archie and jughead double digest?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " you wanna go in the bedroom? it\u0092s a little more comfortable.", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " okay.  oh wait! umm, did you send those contracts to milan?", "answer": " if this is your idea of sexy talk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " no seriously, y\u0092know the contracts i gave you, did you overnight them?", "answer": " what contracts?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay please tell me that this is just one of your jokes that you do that i don\u0092t get.", "answer": " like what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " y\u0092know, like the thing when you put the phone in your pants?  tag! i\u0092m serious! this isn\u0092t funny! those contracts absolutely had to go out today!", "answer": " rach, i\u0092m sorry, but you didn\u0092t give me any contracts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yes i did! and i put a little post-it on it that said, \"must go out today,\" and underlined today three times and, and then i put a little heart in the corner because i didn\u0092t want to seem to bossy.", "answer": " i\u0092m telling you, you never gave them to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " y\u0092know what tag, if we went down to the office you would see those contracts sitting on your desk.", "answer": " no, i would see you looking embarrassed because they are not on my desk!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " or maybe you would see me looking embarrassed because you are talking on the phone with your crotch!", "answer": " you wanna go down to the office right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no! come on its late, we\u0092re not gonna go down to the office.", "answer": " okay i understand.  i wouldn\u0092t want to be proved wrong either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " all right, it won\u0092t go down any further. it\u0092s stuck.", "answer": " ugh. well, we\u0092re just gonna have to jump.  yeah. now, we\u0092re gonna have to make sure to land to the right of that patch of ice, okay? not hit the dumpster on the other side and uh, and try to avoid that-that weird brownish red stuff in the middle. so, when you get down there\u009ayou go up to the roof and you let me in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh whoa-whoa wait a minute! i have to do it?!", "answer": " yeah! oh yeah, you\u0092ll be fine! it-it\u0092ll be uh, just like bungy jumping. y\u0092know? but instead of bouncing back up you-you won\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " what if i smack my head on the concrete?", "answer": " well, i\u0092m gonna lie to you joey, it\u0092s a possibility.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  i don\u0092t know ross! i-i tell you what, let\u0092s flip to see who does it, okay? you-you call it in the air, all right?", "answer": " oh, all right.  tails!  can you-can you see what it is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " okay. well, you be careful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " what? no! no ross! no-no! stop! i\u0092m not jumping! okay, look i have an audition tomorrow and i can\u0092t go if i break my leg.", "answer": " well i\u0092m jumping! i have a son! okay? he won\u0092t have a father if-if i die!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  what? what? what?", "answer": " ohh! ohhhh! were you sleeping sweetie? i\u0092m sorry. here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay! feel free to look, but i\u0092m telling you those contracts are not on this desk.", "answer": " oh how can you possibly know? look at this mess, tag! i mean, this is what i\u0092m talking about! you have to be organized! you\u0092ve got newspapers! you\u0092ve got magazines! you got\u0097ohh!  and who is this chippy? a little young for you tag, but whatever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " it\u0092s my sister.", "answer": " okay, very cute braces. anyway y\u0092know what, the point is tag, start looking because you are going to find those contracts on your desk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " so when do you imagine you gave them to me? in the morning or in the afternoon?", "answer": " in the afternoon. mr. zelner came into my office after lunch. he put them on my desk, and then i put a post-it on it  that said, \"must go out today.\" so you just keep looking in there! all right? commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " it\u0092s not here.", "answer": " puzzler. a bit of a puzzle. why don\u0092t you um, check the copy room, maybe you left the contracts in there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " how could i have left them in the copy room?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know tag! how can your genitals make phone calls? okay? it\u0092s not a perfect world! just go please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " fine.", "answer": " thank you.  hello?  i still don\u0092t get it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " are you still awake?", "answer": " yeah! you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " you do know that was me who just said that right?  hey. as long as we\u0092re both", "answer": "  yeah?  i hope you\u0092re not thinking about cleaning the living room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " man, i\u0092m starving! what the hell was i thinking at dinner?! \"do you want soup or salad?\" both! always order both!", "answer": "  y\u0092know, y\u0092know i\u0092m lookin\u0092 and i don\u0092t think anyone\u0092s home here. i say we just break the window, crawl through, and-and y\u0092know explain later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " yeah? really? no one\u0092s home?", "answer": " i don\u0092t think so. hello?  when you get in there\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " what?! what are you doing?!", "answer": " do you know what just happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " yeah. we-we had sex and then we fell asleep.", "answer": " no. we were in the middle of sex\u009aand you fell asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  monica?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " i was giving you some of my best moves, and you missed it. so please wake up so we can do it right!", "answer": " okay. okay, i\u0092m ready. come on big fella!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " give me the good stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yeah!  no! no! no! don\u0092t fall asleep! okay, i am going to make you some coffee.  and i probably won\u0092t spill coffee grounds all over the kitchen floor.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092m up! i\u0092m up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hi! i got you some coffee. to, uh\u009a  \u009afair enough. so! do you got anything for me?", "answer": " still no luck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh my god! did you check your entire desk! did you check all the drawers!", "answer": " do you want me to check again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well, it\u0092s not out here. is there any chance it could be in your office?", "answer": "  y\u0092know, i don\u0092t-i don\u0092t know. let me, let me check.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  any luck?", "answer": " can i see you in my office for a minute?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  yeah?  you found them!!  y\u0092know what? i\u0092m not even going to gloat. i\u0092m just really relived this whole thing is over.", "answer": " you put these on my desk!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i did not!", "answer": " oh really? so you\u0092re saying they just slid out of your bottom drawer, crawled across the floor, then jumped on to my desk?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " how did you know they were in my bottom drawer?", "answer": "  i am so hot for you right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh my god! how did you get back here?! a disembodied voice:  phoebe buffay?!", "answer": "  fire alarm?  oh! hi, officer\u0097fireman, can-can i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " we found your fire alarm in the trash chute.", "answer": " that\u0092s not mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " yes it is.", "answer": " how do you know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " the next time you want to dump a fire alarm in a trash chute, don\u0092t wrap it in a blanket that says, \"property of phoebe buffay not monica.\"", "answer": " okay do you\u0097okay, do you have a search warrant? because the last time i checked this was still america!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " please reattach this, it\u0092s against the law to disconnect them.", "answer": " fine!  but please god; tell me how to stop them from going off!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " there\u0092s a reset button under the plastic cover.", "answer": " there\u0092s a reset button?! ugh, thank you! thank you!  there\u0092s a reset button! my god! why didn\u0092t i see that!  reset button, reset button, where is there a reset button?  oh here it is!  oh!  ohh, god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " okay, do-do you have a good grip?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " okay, i\u0092m going to start climb down you now.", "answer": " all right! just hurry up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " okay. now-now-now should i climb down your front so we\u0092re face to face or-or should i climb down your back so we\u0092re-we\u0092re butt to face.", "answer": " i think face to face.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i would say that.", "answer": " face to face, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " okay, here i go.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": "  oh my\u009a how much do you weigh ross?!", "answer": " i prefer not to answer that right now, i\u0092m still carrying a little holiday weight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " y\u0092know, when we talked about face to face, i don\u0092t think we thought it all the way through.", "answer": " so what do you want me to do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  m-maybe i should hang and you can climb down", "answer": "  yeah? maybe we should talk about that for a little while!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " it\u0092s still looks pretty far!", "answer": " it\u0092s not that far! just drop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " that really was some of your best work.", "answer": " hm-hmm, i told you!  i can\u0092t believe that i\u0092ve only got two hours before i call in sick for work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " i have to be up in seven minutes.", "answer": " well, you\u0092re not gonna believe this, but if you have seven minutes\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " do you wanna?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}]